bigseagames.com 2011-12-17

# Privacy Policy | Big Fish Games, Inc.

Last modified: September 8, 2011

We at Big Fish Games have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. **By accessing and/or using this Big Fish Games Web site or any Big Fish Games product or service available on or through this web site (each, a " **Big Fish Games Offering** "), you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.**

## INFORMATION THAT WE MAY COLLECT

### Personally Identifiable Information:

We may collect the following information when you sign up with a Big Fish Games Offering:

  * First name, last name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number
  * credit or debit card information, or other payment details, depending on your form of payment.

### IP Address:

When a user accesses a Big Fish Games Offering, we may collect the IP address that requested the display of such Big Fish Games Offering.

### Sign Up and Survey information:

Any information you provide to us, and any information you choose to share about yourself as part of your use of any Big Fish Games Offering, will be stored as entered.

### Cookies:

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we and our service providers may transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as storage of items in your shopping cart between visits and personalized Big Fish Games advertisements on other Web sites.

### Other Information Collected:

We may receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Big Fish Games, if your computer supports such capabilities. The Web browser or client software that you use to access Big Fish Games Offerings may transmit certain geographic information and information regarding the capabilities or features of your computer and/or software to us. We may also track other types of information, such as what games users download and install, any download errors, what games users purchase, how long our users have been participating in any Big Fish Games Offerings, the last time a user accessed a Big Fish Games Offering, user behavior, gameplay, and whether a user has won any of our games, sweepstakes, contests or other promotions featured on a Big Fish Games Offering.

### Social Networking Sites:

If you access one of our social games ("Social Games"), Big Fish Games may receive information about your social networking site profile, including without limitation your first, last and user names, and social networking site profile ID and icon, in accordance with the terms of such social networking site.

If you use a Social Game via your social network page or use a Social Game on someone else's page, we may record information regarding the use of that Social Game, and we may collect other information that is visible on your social network page in accordance with the relevant terms of use associated with that social networking site.

If you invite new members into your Social Games network or send messages through Social Games, we may collect and maintain on secure servers the information associated with those messages, including email addresses and content.

## SECURITY OF COLLECTED INFORMATION

Big Fish Games takes all reasonable precautions to safeguard the privacy of your data. All data that we collect is stored on one or more secure database servers that cannot be accessed from outside our corporate network. Outside of our network, the only access to this data is that provided through the Big Fish Games Offerings. Through the Big Fish Games Offerings, access to personal information is completely controlled by user-defined e-mail addresses and passwords. Within our company, access to data is secured through a private user ID and password known only to personnel who have a need to know such information to perform their essential job functions. All employees of Big Fish Games are legally bound by a nondisclosure agreement that prevents the disclosure of any corporate or customer information to other parties.

## USE OF COLLECTED INFORMATION

We may use your username, e-mail address, and password to uniquely identify you as a user on a Big Fish Games Offering. We may use or display your username for the purposes of rankings, competitions or sweepstakes, chat identification, and/or game high scores.

Subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy, we may use your contact information to process our newsletters and/or e-mail campaigns. Your contact information will allow us to notify you about new features, enhancements, resolution of site problems, handle and/or route your customer support questions and issues, and inform you of upgrade opportunities, sweepstakes, contests, prizes, and/or special events.

If our "Tell a friend" feature is available within a particular Big Fish Games Offering and you choose to participate in it, your e-mail and IP addresses will be shared with the person to whom you send a game to using this feature. We may also use an IP address to exercise our ability to restrict access to the site by users who have violated our Terms of Service.

We use cookies to enhance your online experience. The information in cookies enables us to run our affiliate programs and provide you with personalized Big Fish Games advertisements on other Web sites; enables you to automatically sign in when you access a Big Fish Games Offering; and offers other operational site activities.

We may use other identifying information collected to calculate aggregate statistics about our user community or for security purposes.

If you access a Social Game, we may use your social networking site profile ID to link your social networking site account with your activities within the Social Game. We may use your social networking site first, last and user names and icon to identify you to the social networking site account you've linked to your activities within the Social Game, as well as for the purposes of rankings, competitions, sweepstakes, game high scores and/or identification to your social network.

If you access a Social Game and provide us with another person's contact information for purposes of delivering information through a Social Game, we may use this information to contact and, if necessary, remind that person that she or he has been invited to join a Social Game or received content through a Social Game. All invitees are provided with the option not to receive further invitations from Big Fish Games.

## SHARING INFORMATION

We share customer information only as described below, and with subsidiaries of Big Fish Games that follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Policy.

### Third Party Service Providers:

We will not share your information with any third parties, except that we may disclose your personal information to third parties who perform services for us, such as credit card processing, prize fulfillment, delivering packages, sending postal mail, analyzing data, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), and providing marketing assistance, including serving ads on our behalf on third party Web sites. Those third parties have access to your information only as necessary to perform their functions, and for no other purposes.

### Business Transfers:

As Big Fish Games continues to grow, we might sell or buy certain subsidiaries and/or business units. In such transactions, customer information is generally one of the transferred assets, but would remain subject to the protections described in this Privacy Policy (unless you consent otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that Big Fish Games or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information would in most cases be one of the transferred assets.

### Protection of Big Fish Games and Others:

We may also disclose your information if there is a violation of the [Terms of Use](http://www.bigfishgames.com/company/terms.html) or other agreements; if we have a good faith belief that the law requires it; or if needed to protect the rights, property or safety of Big Fish Games, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with entities for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### With Your Consent:

Apart from what is described above, you will receive notice when information about you might otherwise go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share that information.

## YOUR CHOICES

### Opt-Out:

With the exception of our Social Games, when you create a customer account with a Big Fish Games Offering, you are automatically registered to receive one or more of our e- newsletters, even if you previously opted out of receiving newsletters at the time you downloaded any game for free trial play. At any time, you may opt-out of receiving these newsletters by selecting the " **unsubscribe** " link at the bottom of any newsletter. We treat each Big Fish Games Offering individually, so if you are receiving mailings from more than one area of our website, if you want to unsubscribe you must do so with respect to each such area individually.

### Opt-In:

If you access a Social Game, you will have the option to receive one or more of our Social Games e-newsletters. If you elect to receive any of such newsletters, you may at any time opt-out of receiving them by selecting the " **unsubscribe** " link at the bottom of the newsletter.

### Cookies:

The Help portion of the toolbar on most Web browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, and how to entirely disable cookies. In addition, if any of our third party service providers that present you with personalized Big Fish Games advertisements on other Web sites is a member of the Network Advertising Initiative, you may opt out of such third party's ad-serving cookies through this link: [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Big Fish Games Offerings' essential features, we recommend that you leave cookies turned on. For example, you may not be able make purchases on Big Fish Games Offerings without having cookies turned on.

### Contact Us:

To review, modify or remove the information you have provided to us, or to contact us with any questions or complaints, please e-mail us at [privacy@bigfishgames.com](mailto:privacy@bigfishgames.com) or write to us at: Big Fish Games Privacy Policy Department, 333 Elliott Avenue West, Suite 200, Seattle, WA 98119 USA.

## LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY SITES

Web sites that link to or from a Big Fish Games Offering may collect personal information about you. If you access our Social Games, this includes, without limitation, any social networking sites that you participate in. Most content offered through Social Games is served or hosted by other Web sites. This Big Fish Games Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, those Web sites.

## CHAT & MESSAGING

Big Fish Games Offerings may operate message boards and/or chat areas where users can exchange ideas and communicate with each other. When posting to a message board or chat area, the information is being made publicly available in an online environment. Any information posted is the sole responsibility of the individual user.

## CHILDREN

We at Big Fish Games do not offer products for purchase by children, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children. If you are under 13, you may use and access the Big Fish Games Offerings only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

Big Fish Games respects the privacy of parents and children and is committed to complying with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to Big Fish Games, he or she can contact us via e-mail at [privacy@bigfishgames.com](mailto:privacy@bigfishgames.com) or postal mail at the address listed below. We will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 13. We recognize the importance of safeguarding the privacy of children and encourage parents to check and monitor their children's use of online activities regularly.

## SAFE HARBOR PROGRAM

Big Fish Games participates in the Safe Harbor program developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Union. We have certified that we adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles agreed upon by the U.S. and the E.U. For more information about the Safe Harbor and to view our certification, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce's [Safe Harbor Web site](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/). To contact Big Fish Games directly about the Safe Harbor program, please e-mail us at [](mailto:safeharbor@bigfishgames.com)[safeharbor@bigfishgames.com](mailto:safeharbor@bigfishgames.com).

## AGREEMENT WITH BIG FISH GAMES POLICIES

By accessing and/or using any of the Big Fish Games Offerings, you signify your understanding of and agreement with this Privacy Policy, and to our [Terms of Use](http://www.bigfishgames.com/company/terms.html). If you do not agree with our policies, please do not access or use any Big Fish Games Offerings.

## CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

We may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "last modified" date at the top of this page. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how Big Fish Games protects your information.
